// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " Which of the following is true about the anonymous inner class?",
    answer: "It has no class name",
    options: [
      "It has no class name",
     "It has no class name",
   "Objects can't be created",
   "It has only methods"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " Which of these class is superclass of every class in Java?",
    answer: "Object class",
    options: [
      "String class",
      "ArrayList class",
      "Abstract class",
      "Object class"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of these method of Object class is used to obtain class of an object at run time?",
    answer: "Class getclass()",
    options: [
      "get()",
      "Class getclass()",
      " void getclass()",
      " None of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: ". Which of these keywords can be used to prevent inheritance of a class?",
       answer: "final",
    options: [
      "final",
      "constant",
      "super",
      "class"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " Which of these can be overloaded?" ,
    answer: "Constructors",
    options: [
      "Methods",
      "Constructors",
      "All of the mentioned",
      " None of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " Which of this keyword can be used in a subclass to call the constructor of superclass?" ,
    answer: "super",
    options: [
      "super",
      " this",
      "extends",
      " extent"
     
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " What is the process of defining a method in a subclass having same name & type signature as a method in its superclass?" ,
    answer: "Method overriding",
    options: [
      "Method overloading",
      "Method overriding",
      " Method hiding",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of these is correct way of calling a constructor having no parameters, of superclass A by subclass B?" ,
    answer: "super();",
    options: [
      "super();",
      "super(void);",
      " superclass.();",
      "super.A();"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: " Which of these is supported by method overriding in Java?" ,
    answer: " Polymorphism",
    options: [
      " Polymorphism",
      " Encapsulation",
      "Abstraction",
      "None of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is a method having same name as that of its class?" ,
    answer: "	 constructor",
    options: [
      "	 constructor",
      "delete",
      "finalize",
      "class" 
     ]
  },
  
  
  
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
  
  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
  ];